Yuval Moshe

A 25 year old B.Cs student (2nd year – Dean's List), with 2.5-years of experience working in the high-tech industry, offering a strong foundation in software engineering and programming principles across multiple platforms, quick to learn and master new technologies, successful working in both teams and self-directed settings.

Phone: 054-4626-873

Email: Yuval1929@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Yuval Moshe GitHub: Yuval-Moshe

Work Experience

Product Manager & QA Engineer (12/2019 - Present)



- Led the research and implementation of in-app analytics, including events characterization, establishing measurable retention KPI's and performing ongoing data mining to extract meaningful growth-related insights.
- Worked constantly on improving our UX with the extent of the onboarding experience and monetization optimization, to align with our unique value proposition.
- Built and executed detailed and well-structured test cases while working closely with the R&D team.

Fraud Analyst (01/2019 - 11/2019)

RSA

- Detected, investigated, and mitigated fraudulent phishing and malware attacks while performing deep analysis on communication networks.
- Worked most and mainly with International vendors and service suppliers.

Education

BA Student, Computer Science (2nd Year)

(11/2019 - Present: Expected Graduation Summer 2022)

University of Ariel

- Dean's List.
- Current GPA 92.59

Skills & Tools

Tools

PyCharm | VS Code | Intellij | Eclipse | Firebase | Google Analytics | GitHub | Workbench | BigQuery.

Technical Skills

- C++
- Java
- Python
- C

- SQL
- Cassandra
- MongoDB
- HTML / CSS

- Git
- Linux

Languages

Hebrew - Native | English - Fluent